Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Once upon a time, in a certain place...
Prehistoric creatures full of personality!
Tirano, Stego, Ammonite,Trilobite.
They've been saying "hi" for 500 million years.
Prehistory! Everybody Say (Roar!)
Ancient, Alright! Future, FLY High!
A herd of mammoths! Run!
Thud thud thud thud! On your marks, get set, go!
Dive deep into serious learning,
and get excited!
Witness a miracle born from fossils.
Dive deep into serious learning,
Playing for real.
The universe begins with passion.
Super happy!
Serious Master Ichthyostega
Dino!
I'm gonna teach you how the real world works!
What are you doing?!
Dino said modern amphibians are better than prehistoric ones,
so I'm beating him up!
You're the one getting beaten up!
But aren't modern amphibians cooler?!
You know nothing at all!
WELCOME TO THE WORLD OF SERIOUS PALEONTOLOGY!
Wait, what?
A script?
Am I supposed to read this?
Um...
"Prehistoric vs. Modern Amphibian Showdown"?
Prehistoric Organisms? Modern Organisms? Amphibian Show-Off Show!
You will brag about the coolest traits
of ancient and modern amphibians.
First...
representing modern species: Japanese Tree Frog!
Hey there!
Next up,
representing prehistoric species
Ichthyostega!
A bit lower, please!
Representing Prehistoric Amphibians
Ichthyostega
Thank you!
Master Ichthyostega!
It's an honor to meet you!
Please, right this way!
He acts like an apprentice...
Host, proceed!
R-Right!
First, Frog-san,
show off your skills!
My toes are like suction cups...
so they're super useful for sticking to walls and stuff!
How's that?
I see.
During the Late Devonian period when Master Ichthyostega lived,
fish ruled the world!
Amidst that,
they evolved from fish and ventured onto land the ultra-early
pioneers of amphibians!
The proof is...
these 7 digits that evolved from fins!
How about that?!
That's pretty cool!
Furthermore!
Master's ribs are ...
thick and heavy!
Is that amazing?
The biggest obstacle for aquatic creatures moving to land is...
gravity!
Master had thick, long ribs to withstand gravity
and protect internal organs!
As a result...
...Master is said to be...
...the first creature in Earth's history
to achieve four-legged walking on land!
The first...
four-legged walker?!
In the Late Devonian,
that first step onto the mainland!
it was a step to survive in a new world,
Late Devonian,
approximately 365 million years ago
the very first step toward the prosperity
of amphibians,
and us mammals later on!
It was also the first step.
So prehistoric creatures were way cooler!
That's not it, Dino!
Discovering great ancient steps through fossils...
and understanding evolution by observing modern life,
that is paleontology!
It's not about which is better;
both are precious and amazing!
Please let me call you Master too!
Ah, go right ahead.
Oh!
Ichthyostega.
You are Master's Tiktaalik!
375-Million-Year-Old Prehistoric Creature
Grandmaster Tiktaalik
You are Master's senior!
The prehistoric creature who did push-ups on land first!
Grandmaster Tiktaalik!
How's that?
Pretty slick, right?
As expected of you!
I'm no match for Grandmaster!
Hail Grandmaster!
Master was acting so arrogant until now...
So this is how vertical hierarchy works!